Many people ask me
Have high blood pressure
Are destined to take medicine for the rest of your life?
If you have been relying on
medicament to force your blood pressure down
afraid for a lifetime
Suffering from side effects
Eight o'clock in the morning
Ming hailed a taxi
Once on the bus
Driver
I'm going to the airport
I'm rushing to catch a plane
Please hurry up
Well, what time do you want to take the flight?
I have a flight at 8:30.
Hey!
Don't be kidding.
I drove to the airport
Half an hour at the fastest
The plane has already flown away.
You're too late
Driver
The plane shouldn't have left yet.
Because
I am the captain of this flight.
Hu Naiwen starts his lecture
I am your old friend, Doctor Hu
Many people ask me
Have high blood pressure
Are destined to take medicine for the rest of your life?
If keep
Forced lowering of blood pressure by drugs
afraid for a lifetime
Suffering from side effects
Today I will share with you
Want to cure high blood pressure
You need to understand a concept
that is more important than taking medicine.
To find out the real reason
I will also tell you
A good way to save life
Cause 1 of high blood pressure: stiff neck
Today I will talk about three causes of high blood pressure
Pay attention
Now many office workers
Or the supervisors are sitting still for too long.
shoulders are staring at the computer.
feel very tired after work.
came home and lay on the sofa again, not wanting to move
Or looking down at your phone
This will cause the shoulder
The neck area
Stiffness prevents blood from flowing to the head
This causes dizziness, headache, swelling of the head, and tinnitus
or
Neck stiffness
Very very bad
So what if this is the case?
Poor blood circulation
This is called blood stasis.
If blood flow is blocked, the brain will be deprived of oxygen.
Therefore, greater force must be used to
transport blood throughout the body
Of course blood pressure will be high, right?
1 point on the elbow to relax the shoulders and neck 2 acupoints to lower blood pressure
Relieve stiff neck and shoulders
A acupoint
Where is this acupuncture point?
It's actually very simple
It is a chǐ zé (Transliteration) acupoint
This chǐ zé (Transliteration) acupoint
Although it is said to be an acupuncture point on the fèi jīng (Transliteration)
But it can soothe
Lung Meridian Problems
and the Fèi yú (Transliteration) acupoint on the back
It can help blood circulation here
This Fèi yú (Transliteration) acupointon the back
It can also affect the blood supply
Poor blood circulation in the neck
That's the problem with this place
Press this chǐ zé (Transliteration) acupoint
You press your left and right hands like this every day
How does it do it?
It's like this
When your palms are facing the ceiling
On the crease of the elbow bend
On the thumb line
This is the acupoint
Just press gently
for three to five minutes.
While pressing
shake your neck like this
Natural blood circulation
The blood circulation in the neck has improved.
Naturally
the blood in the carotid artery flows to the brain.
Therefore, the blood supply to the brain is sufficient.
Blood pressure naturally drops.
I'll teach you a trick, knock
When knocking like this
Because you're knocking
But sometimes knockit a little bit above
Sometimes knock the bottom.
The result
Sometimes knockthe real acupuncture point
So there is this effect
So I'll teach you how to knock
You just keep knocking, knocking.
Knock like this
In addition to this acupuncture point
There are two more
Acupuncture points that can enhance your blood circulation
One iszú sān lǐ (Transliteration)
One issān yīn jiāo(Transliteration)
This in the past
I have mentioned this in many programs.
knockzú sān lǐ (Transliteration)in the same way
knocksān yīn jiāo(Transliteration)in the same way
Compared to pressing directly
Maybe you're not pressing accurately, right?
If you knock like this
There's almost a chance to hit it right
Did you know
Knock more to maintain your health
can also prolong life
But have to remind you
If you are a pregnant woman
Don't knock onsān yīn jiāo(Transliteration)
Don't press it, okay?
Reason 2 for high blood pressure: anger and tension
Do you know when you are angry?
Sympathetic nervous system hyperactivity
The peripheral blood vessels constrict
At this time
The blood will not be able to deliver oxygen directly
to all parts of the body.
At this time
He has high blood pressure.
I have a patient
He has a wife who is probably around fifty years old.
A little bit fat
She told me
Her blood pressure is always around 200.
went to see a western doctor but nothing could lower blood pressure.
took a lot of blood pressure medication.
There are only six blood pressure lowering drugs
She has tried all six.
It didn't come down either.
Then she came to me
I gave her treatment
After a period of treatment, you know
Her blood pressure dropped to 140-150
Very happy
Tell everyone everywhere
Doctor Hu cured my blood pressure.
I told her then
Don't talk nonsense
I didn't treat your high blood pressure.
You cured it yourself
Why?
Because you listened to me
You do whatever I tell you to do.
Then I prescribed some medicine.
But this medicine
It helps you
feel less nervous.
When your emotions are high
Then the sympathetic nerves are hyperactive.
Sympathetic nervous system hyperactivity
The most important thing is
that it changes your heart.
The heart either beats very fast
or beats very strongly.
At this time
Your blood pressure is just very high when measured.
But if you
Your temper is not that easy
to anger.
Then every day is happy.
As long as you relieve your own emotions.
That's good.
So I prescribed you the medicine
It's a mood-relief drug.
Then you cooperated again
Let your own emotions cool down
So you will be cured.
This is not me healing you.
Chrysanthemum tea and it, can improve mood and lower blood pressure
Let me tell you the first one
The first step is
Drinking tea can soothe your mood
Did you know
What kind of tea is good to drink?
chrysanthemum
It's a chrysanthemum
You put about ten chrysanthemums
in a mug.
Whether it is yellow chrysanthemum or white chrysanthemum
Or wild chrysanthemum
As long as it is chrysanthemum
Throw some chrysanthemums down
Then brew with hot water
Wait until it brews and becomes fragrant.
When the chrysanthemum in the water is steeped.
Once it has a little fragrance, you can drink it.
If you want to make it taste better
You can add some licorice
Or add some wolfberry and it will be fine
tell you about tea
What about this tea?
It needs to be cooked a bit
to bring out the flavor.
It's calledgān mài dà zǎo tāng (Transliteration)
gān mài dà zǎo tāng (Transliteration)
If you drink it as soup
you can also drink it as tea.
What is meant by "soup" is to cook it a bit more concentrated.
What is meant by "tea" is to cook it a bit lighter.
Then today, I’ll let you turn it into tea to drink.
Licorice root about 4 qián (Transliteration)
Wheat 1 liǎng (Transliteration)
The best kind of wheat is fú xiǎo mài (Transliteration)
So-called fú xiǎo mài (Transliteration) is lighter.
What does "lighter" mean exactly?
It is the wheat
that has been stored
for a longer time
When buy it at a Chinese medicine store
You buy fú xiǎo mài (Transliteration)
Licorice, 4 qián (Transliteration)
Wheat 1liǎng(Transliteration)
About 12 jujubes
The so-called jujube is red jujube
Don't use black dates.
Red dates are good for this place.
Use 1500cc of water
Put it in the pot and cook
Cook to 1000cc
Then drink it as tea for the day
Can drink every day
You are in a good mood
It's not easy to get angry
The lady mentioned above
I also let her drinkgān mài dà zǎo tāng (Transliteration)
So the mood becomes better.
Oh, so didn't drink before
Is that what say?
If you say it again, I'll be angry.
Then after drinking it, they will say
If you do this again, I'll be angry.
Cause of high blood pressure 3: Cold weather, one thing raises blood pressure.
Why blood pressure rises
From our perspective of traditional Chinese medicine
Chinese medicine treatment
It is from external factors,
weather
Fēng huǒrè shī zào hán (Transliteration), etc.
What is the reason for your high blood pressure?
Find the reasons from the emotions
Joy, anger, worry, thought, sadness, fear, surprise.
Which one did you commit?
Then, let's treat the blood pressure.
good
I tell you
We use traditional Chinese medicine to analyze blood pressure
Cold will increase blood pressure
Okay, let's use the terminology of Western medicine.
Very simple
When it's cold, the blood vessels around you contract
Why does it shrink?
It's because of the sympathetic nervous system hyperactivity
Sympathetic nerves are excited, and the peripheral blood vessels contract
resulting in high blood pressure and blood
flowing to the middle area.
Then you measure your blood pressure
Of course it is high, right?
ok
The blood pressure measurement is high
Actually, how is it
When you are cold, it is to protect your body heat
from being dissipated from this area.
So the blood stays in the middle
Therefore, the body will be hotter and
Not only that
Blood pressure will of course rise
The blood pressure is getting high.
This allows the blood to be delivered
to various places.
In that case
Natural
Blood pressure is at the point
where the need has been met.
Blood pressure will naturally drop, right?
ok
At this time
Cold is one of the causes of high blood pressure
What are you going to do when it's that cold?
Very simple
You put on a piece of clothing to keep your body warm.
Or take a warm pack.
Keep your hands and feet warm
Naturally, the blood pressure will not be high.
It's such a simple principle
But we are not
We often take
blood pressure medication.
You need to know at this time
You may be lowering your blood pressure too much.
It is also easy to cause the so-called
Cerebral thrombosis stroke
or other stroke
Pain, tension, worry
Blood pressure will also increase
Didn't we just say that?
External factors Cold
What about the internal factors?
Maybe nervous
Maybe troubled
These may cause
And pain, these may
ok
Pain, tension, worry
Sympathetic nerves also become hyperactive
At this time, the peripheral blood vessels also contract.
This shrinks
Heartbeat speeds up
Increased blood pressure
and
The real reason is that the pain is relieved
Or maybe the tension is gone.
Or the trouble is gone.
I tell you that your blood pressure will naturally decrease.
So you have to thank your high blood pressure
It allows you to respond immediately
to bad situations and improve them.
Taking medicine all the time may cause permanent high blood pressure
I want to tell you something
If you only use medication
to forcibly lower blood pressure
You will feel dizzy
Headache
nausea
The heartbeat slows down.
Or palpitations
These side effects
Blood pressure-lowering medication
Usually there
are several
For example, diuretics
Vasodilators, etc.
Its purpose is to force the body's blood
pressure to drop.
What are their side effects?
Will cause
Kidney burden
It may also cause the Cardiac Muscle to thicken.
I tell you
Because the blood pressure is too low
The heart feels
that it cannot pump blood everywhere.
So the Cardiac Muscle
have to use great force
The force is getting stronger
The harder it works
At that time, the Cardiac Muscle
It starts to get thicker
Thickening of the Cardiac Muscle
may cause permanent high blood pressure
have high blood pressure?
Still need to
undergo careful inspection
Don't judge easily
It's hypertension
So
Take blood pressure medication
Don't take the wrong medicine.
didn't heal body.
Friends
who are taking blood pressure medication
Watch this episode
Think carefully
Or find your doctor
and discuss it with him.
How to make your body
better
3 natural things to protect your heart and lower your blood pressure
Friends with high blood pressure
In addition to medicament
You can also stabilize
your blood pressure through diet
Introducing you three natural foods
First, celery
Second, nuts
Third, banana
Celery
There is an ingredient
Called apigenin
Can protect cardiovascular
Nuts can help
stabilize blood pressure
Eat a few nuts a day
For example,
A small handful
That's it
Don't eat too much
banana
Rich in potassium
Able to maintain a stable heartbeat
Prevent high blood pressure and stroke
Bananas should not exceed two per day
If you have renal insufficiency
or people with kidney failure
At this time
It will also cause high blood pressure, right?
That kind of person
Don't eat bananas
Or ask
Let your doctor know.
A message
From this side of the earth
It only takes a few seconds
to get to the other end
And an idea
from outside the mind
Enter the mind
Sometimes
It takes a while to change
Watch this episode
A clearer understanding
of high blood pressure
Don't just think you
have to take medicine
for high blood pressure.
and can't stop taking it.
In fact
we should find the right way to improve our lives.
Friends who like this video
Please click "Super Thanks" below the video
Give us support